let questions=[
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "A number when divided by 899 gives a remainder 63. if the same number is divided by 29,the remainder will be : ",
        answer: "5",
        options: [
            "10",
            "5",
            "4", 
            "2",           
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "1/0.04 is equal to :",
        answer: "25",
        options: [
            "1/40",
            "2/5",
            "5/2",
            "25",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "A six digit number is formed by repeating a three digit number; for example, 6256 or 8678 etc. Any number of this form is always divisible by:",
        answer: "1001",
        options: [
            "7 only",
            "11 only",
            "13 only",
            "1001",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "The smallest number to be added to 1000,so that 45 divides the sum exactly,is: ",
        answer: "35",
        options:[
            "35",
            "80",
            "20",
            "10",
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:"Which of the following numbers will always divide a six digit number of the form xyxyxy(where 1<=x<=9,1<=y<=9)?",
        answer: "10101",
        options:[
            "1010",
            "10101",
            "11011",
            "11010",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:"The divisor is 25 times the quotient and 5 times the remainder.if the quotient is 16,the dividend is:",
        answer:"6480",
        options:[
            "6400",
            "6480",
            "400",
            "480",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:"The product of two positive numbers is 11520 and their quotient is 9/5.Find the difference of two number.",
        answer:"64",
        options:[
            "60",
            "64",
            "74",
            "70",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:"A student was asked to multiply a number by 3/2 but he divided that number by 3/2. His result was 10 less than the correct answer. The number was:",
        answer:"12",
        options:[
            "10",
            "12",
            "15",
            "20",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:"If 3/4 of the difference of 2 1/4 and 1 2/3 is subtracted from 2/3 of 3 1/4 the result is ",
        answer:"83/48",
        options:[
            "-48/83",
            "48/83",
            "-83/48",
            "83/48",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:10,
        question:"The sum of first sixty numbers from one to sixty is divisible by",
        answer: "61",
        options:[
            "13",
            "59",
            "60",
            "61",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:11,
        question:"The product of two numbers is 9375 and the quotient, when the larger one is divided by the smaller,is 15. The sum of the numbers is:",
        answer: "400",
        options:[
            "395",
            "380",
            "400",
            "425",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question:"The digit in unit's place of the product (2153) power 167 is:  ",
        answer: "7",
        options: [
            "1",
            "3",
            "7",
            "9",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question:"The digit in the units place of [(251) power 98 + (21) power 29 -(106) power 100 + (705) power 35 - 16 power 4 + 259] is:",
        answer: "4",
        options:[
            "1",
            "4",
            "5",
            "6",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question:"By interchanging the digits of a two digit number we get a number which is four times the original number which minus 24. If the units digit of the original number exceeds its ten's digit by 7,then original number is ",
        answer:"29",
        options:[
            "29",
            "36",
            "58",
            "18",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:15,
        question:"There is a number consisting of two digits, the digit in the units place is twice that in the tens place and if 2 be subtracted from the sum of the digits, the difference is equal to 1/6th of the number. the number is ",
        answer:"24",
        options:[
            "26",
            "25",
            "24",
            "23",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question:"What is the unit digit of 279 + 167 * 342?",
        answer:"3",
        options:[
            "1",
            "3",
            "5",
            "8",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question:"If the unit digit of (433 * 456 * 43N)is (N+2), then what is the value of N?",
        answer:"6",
        options:[
            "1",
            "8",
            "3",
            "6",

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question:"If a number 657423547 x 46 is divisible by 11, then find the value of x",
        answer:"9",
        options:[
            "7",
            "9",
            "8",
            "6",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question:"The last digit of 3 power 40 is:",
        answer:"1",
        options:[
            "1",
            "3",
            "7",
            "9",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question:"What will be the unit digit in the product 7 power 105",
        answer:"7",
        options:[
            "5",
            "7",
            "9",
            "1",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question:"What is the sum of two consecutive even numbers, the difference of whose square is 84",
        answer:"42",
        options:[
            "38",
            "34",
            "42",
            "46",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:22,
        question:"What is the arithmetic mean of first 20 odd natural numbers?",
        answer:"20",
        options:[
            "19",
            "17",
            "22",
            "20",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:23,
        question:"The sum of all the natural numbers from 51 to 100 is ",
        answer:"3775",
        options:[
            "5050",
            "4275",
            "4025",
            "3775",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:24,
        question:"The sum of all the 3-digit numbers, each of which on division by 5 leaves remainder 3,is",
        answer:"99090",
        options:[
            "180",
            "1550",
            "6995",
            "99090",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:25,
        question:"Which one of the following is a factor of the sum of first twenty-five natural numbers?",
        answer:"13",
        options:[
            "26",
            "24",
            "13",
            "12",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 26,
        question:"The sum of the squares of 3 consecutive positive numbers is 365. The sum of the numbers is",
        answer:"33",
        options:[
            "30",
            "33",
            "36",
            "45",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 27,
        question:"What is the sum of all natural numbers between 1 and 100 which are multiples of 7?",
        answer:"735",
        options:[
            "735",
            "675",
            "745",
            "705",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 28,
        question:"The sum of three consecutive even numbers is always divisible by",
        answer:"6",
        options:[
            "12",
            "6",
            "18",
            "24",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 29,
        question:"The product of two even consecutive numbers is 168.Find the sum of these numbers.",
        answer:"26",
        options:[
            "20",
            "22",
            "24",
            "26",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 30,
        question:"The sum of four consecutive odd numbers is 328.Find the largest number.",
        answer:"85",
        options:[
            "85",
            "98",
            "79",
            "97",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 31,
        question:"Six numbers are arranged in decreasing order. The average of the first five numbers is 30 and the average of the last five numbers is 25.The difference of the first and the last numbers is:",
        answer:"25",
        options:[
            "20",
            "25",
            "5",
            "30",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 32,
        question:"The sum of three consecutive integers is 51.The middle one is:",
        answer:"17",
        options:[
            "14",
            "15",
            "16",
            "17",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 33,
        question:"The smallest possible three place decimal number is:",
        answer:"None of the above",
        options:[
            "0.012",
            "0.123",
            "0.111",
            "None of the above",

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 34,
        question:"The smallest number of five digits exactly divisible by 476 is ",
        answer:"10472",
        options:[
            "47600",
            "10000",
            "10476",
            "10472",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:35,
        question:"The least number of five digits which has 123 as a factor is ",
        answer:"10086",
        options:[
            "10037",
            "10086",
            "10081",
            "10063",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:36,
        question:"When 335 is added to 5A7, the result is 8B2.8B2 is divisible by 3.What is largest posible value of A?",
        answer:"4",
        options:[
            "8",
            "2",
            "1",
            "4",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:37,
        question:"If a number is as much greater than 31 as it is less than 75,then the number is ",
        answer:"53",
        options:[
            "106",
            "44",
            "74",
            "53",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:38,
        question:"Which is the largest of the following fractions?  2/3,3/5,8/11,11/17",
        answer:"8/11",
        options:[
            "8/11",
            "3/5",
            "11/17",
            "2/3",

        ]
    },
    {
        numb:39,
        question:"What is the largest two digit prime number?",
        answer:"97",
        options:[
            "91",
            "93",
            "97",
            "99",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:40,
        question:"Find the number that is as much greater than 49 as is less than 95.",
        answer:"72",
        options:[
            "23",
            "55",
            "72",
            "76",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:41,
        question:"What is that least digit that must be added to the product 5786*5784 to make it a perfect square?",
        answer:"1",
        options:[
            "1",
            "6",
            "5",
            "4",
            

        ]
    
    },
    {
        numb:42,
        question:"One fourth of a tank holds 135 litres of water.What part of the tank is full if it contains 180 litres of water?",
        answer:"1/3",
        options:[
            "2/5",
            "2/3",
            "1/3",
            "1/6",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:43,
        question:"1/5 of a number exceeds 1/7 of the same number by 10. The number is:",
        answer:"175",
        options:[
            "125",
            "150",
            "175",
            "200",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:44,
        question:"If 3 times a number exceeds its 3/5 by 60,then what is the number?",
        answer:"25",
        options:[
            "25",
            "35",
            "45",
            "60",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:45,
        question:"Half of 1 percent written as a decimal is --",
        answer:"",
        options:[
            "0.2",
            "0.02",
            "0.05",
            "0.005",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:46,
        question:"If one-third of a number is 15, then three-tenth of the number is",
        answer:"54",
        options: [
            "35",
            "36",
            "45",
            "54",

        ]
    },
    {
        numb:47,
        question:"Express 45 minutes as the fraction of one day.",
        answer:"1/32",
        options:[
            "1/40",
            "1/32",
            "1/60",
            "1/24",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:48,
        question:"A number exceeds its one-fifth by 20.The number is ",
        answer:"25",
        options: [
            "100",
            "25",
            "20",
            "5",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:49,
        question:"0.1 and 5/8 of a bamboo are in mud and water respectively and the rest of length 2.75m is above water. what is the length of the bamboo?",
        answer:"",
        options:[
            "10m",
            "30m",
            "27.5m",
            "20m",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:50,
        question:"If one-nineth of a certain number exceeds its one-tenth by 4,the number is",
        answer:"360",
        options:[
            "320",
            "360",
            "400",
            "440",
        ]
    }
]